Hello friends, I am your Subjective
Koyal and a warm welcome to Ankit Pani Step YouTube channel.
Friends, if we
talk about marriage, we all know that it is a
very special event in everyone's life
and there is a new beginning,
everyone is happy and if we talk about India's space, then if we
talk about status tips, then
it tells that in India a lot of
money is spent on weddings and generally on an
average Rs 20 lakh to 5 crore is spent
and a lot of guests also come, who
generally have a big emphasis on the wedding,
everyone wants that
their wedding should go well and be perfect,
but no one knows this, see, the
train always remains as per the wish, any
situation can happen at any time which you do not want,
it can happen, the wedding may get cancelled, some
date may get extended, bangles are lost
in the wedding or some losses are incurred, then
what happens in that is that there is a lot of stress
that whenever you have already paid money
to these people in advance, when did you talk about the channel, the
train, the hotel, the decoration, there is a lot of stress  There is a
type of money which you have already seen
and if ever any event gets cancelled or any kind of
moment comes
which causes caffeine, then to
avoid all these, a perfect solution is
wedding insurance in which you already have a
cover, if there is any unforeseen event or
any loss, all the
money is given to you by the company and you become
tension free, so there are many
companies in India too which
provide wedding insurance, so in today's video I am going to
tell you which losses are covered
and which are not, how much does it
cost, for how many days is the insurance,
what are the benefits, what are the disadvantages, we will
talk about all these things, so this is the biggest thing,
but there are many companies, let
us first talk about Future Generali,
apart from this, if we talk about it,
Bajaj Financer also does it,
ICICI Bank, there are many
companies which do insurance, so one by one
I will tell you, first of all if we
talk about Future Generali, then see, they have
told that they add a key on the website that
if you have got insurance done  It also
depends on how innocent you were, you
want to make a difference, you want to make an insurance of 10 lakhs or
20 lakhs, generally the premium is from
half percent to two percent,
if you support me, I would say that
even one percent is a premium, so if you
waste your time and get
insurance of 10 lakhs, then only a
premium of 10 thousand rupees will be charged and if there is any loss, if there is any
theft, any
disability occurs, any accident happens, there is an
app, it is said that there is a fire somewhere,
anything happens, then the
companies will give you the loss amount of ₹1000000, so first of all let us
talk about what are the problems, then
this will bring fruit, see if there is a
marriage cancellation, the marriage gets cancelled
due to this or it gets postponed, then you have
blocked the messages hole, the
advance for this has been given to the Pandit, the
decoration has been done,
money has been given to the application, to the photographers, to the DJ, to the
flower seller  Whatever money has been given, all of it will be
covered in this. These losses will be borne by the
insurance company. Sir, we
see that where there is a very high cost wedding, the
accommodation there costs
Rs. 50 per room for a party.
All these things are judgment rules.
Secondly, he told about damage to the property
where the wedding is taking place, if there is any damage to
your house, any restaurant,
any damage to the decoration,
any of your side's entire
loss, whatever the decision is, all those things will be
covered, whether it catches fire or anything else.
Apart from this, it has been seen in many grand weddings that
jewellery
and vitamins get stolen, so all those things, all the
valuable items, all of them are
covered. Jewellery,
precious stones, appliances, whatever
gifts you have to give to the guests, all those
things will be covered. Apart from this, if an
accident happens, if you ever have an
accident with the bride or any member of the group you are pointing to, friends.  If any
disability occurs or death occurs, then
all those things have been proven.
Apart from this, if we talk about
any theft from the gallery or any money has been
stolen anywhere, then all that will be
covered in it. So, there are many such things which are
chances in this, we see that the forest is very
wide, then we see that the
whole time itself becomes wide, so
all this will be news. There are some things which are
not news, in which
they have said that congenital disease, sugar, if you have any
disease from the beginning, the light is off, that
student's low is hidden and due to which
something goes down, then that will not be covered.
Apart from this, if you have bought a vehicle or a truck
due to which your health deteriorates,
that too will not be covered. You have
not taken any trusted advice from any doctor,
you have taken any medicine due to which your health
deteriorates, that too will not be covered. And if
someone goes out or becomes restless, then
we will not be interested in that thing. So
now it depends when Happy Wedding
Insurance  Let's take it, you have to describe the insurance company
below,
you have to tell all those things that chapter
improved tax difference companies do not have,
whatever your closure is, the company will tell all the things,
apart from this, this is only about future
dinner, okay, apart from this, if we talk about
ICICI Lombard thing, then after
cutting it in this length, I will give you this page and its link, so
they have given all the things
that if the wedding gets cancelled, then
what things are covered, robbery and murder, damages to
property, what things are followed,
personal accident and public
liability,
you can see the link of all those things in the page description, then you will get to know whether the
chain is fruitful or not,
thank you, and if we talk then a question
also arises
for post-depression, so this Jangli is
insured till the next day of the wedding ending,
Jangli is insured for a week,
whose insurance is there because if we talk about it in India, the
guideline is
very long, its duration is 272, then it
becomes insurance of 527
You can get complete details from them by talking to their customer care,
so apart from this,
I have already told you about this, Yukti
Insurance features Fingers and
apart from this, HDFC Agro also does it, if
you have some small insurance needs, then for that, if we
talk about Bajaj Finserv, then in
Bajaj Finserv you can see
wedding dress insurance, that is, they
insure only wedding night dresses,
apart from this they do Jubilee Year Term
Insurance, they do
term insurance up to 500 for oily fry and its
premium is only 349 on that number, so in this
way this company does English romance in different ways, it is
not very much in trend in India also, but if there is
knowledge of it, then people will start getting insurance, you will
get a lot of benefit from the phone
because as I told you, the messages that are received are
quite big, the budget increases and
those who do not get the thread done on their own, then
all those people have to spend, so to
avoid this, the best
option is to avoid wedding, it is auspicious, so if
you did not get the information through this video, if you liked the
video then like it  You can
subscribe to our channel's fan club
and share it with as many injured people as possible
so that they too will have knowledge about
terrorists.